365greetings.com 2010-12-01

# Free Birthday Cards, Free Greeting Cards, electronic greeting card, Printable Cards, Wedding cards - Privacy

##### 365greetings.com Privacy Policy 

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. The following policies are only in effect for the Web pages, newsletters, discussion lists and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by Free Ecards, (Free Ecards includes all Web sites and certain other Internet media properties hyper linked from the Free Ecards home page.) The following discloses our Privacy Policy. 

##### What information are you collecting and how are you collecting it? 

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers, that serve as that computer's "Internet Protocol" IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any Web site within the Free Ecards , our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, and to investigate misuse of the Free Ecards , its users, or to cooperate with law enforcement. See also Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties? We do not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals. Our Web servers do not automatically record e-mail addresses of the visitors. 

##### What are cookies? 

From time to time, Free Ecards or its advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of Free Ecards you have visited or customized, so the next time you visit, those pages may be readily accessible. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. Our advertisers and we may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you see on our site. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended. 

##### We use third-party advertising companies

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. 1\. The advertising networks may place a 3rd party cookie on your computer

2\. Such a cookie may be used to tailor ad content both on the site you are visiting as well as other sites within that network that you may visit in the future. 

You can opt out from these by using NAI opt-out tool at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [Click Here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

##### How do you use single-pixel gifs? 

Free Ecards and its advertisers may use single-pixel gif images, sometimes referred to as web bugs or web beacons, to count Web page accesses and gather some general statistical information. Free Ecards does not gather personal information through the use of these images. Our advertisers may use single-pixel gifs that can track personal information from cookies that may have been previously placed on a user's computer by an advertiser. 

##### What information do you collect when I register for something? 

Free Ecards offers access to some services that require registration. We may use your registration contact information to send notification to you of Free Ecards products and services by e-mail and/or postal mail. We also may share that information with our clients. Our clients may send you promotional material that is related to the topic of the service for which you registered. We may also use your IP address internally and share it with third parties. See Will you disclose the information that you collect to outside third parties? 

##### What other information do you request? 

We may also request your e-mail address or mailing address for the purposes of conducting a survey or to provide additional services (for example, subscriptions to e-mail newsletters, announcement lists or information about conferences and trade shows). Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested. We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy that means that we do not sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent or as permitted by this Privacy Policy.

We may from time to time send e-mail announcing new Free Ecards products and services. Except as stated above, Free Ecards will not send you e-mail that you have not agreed to receive. If you choose to supply your postal address in an online form, you may receive postal mailings from other third party companies. 

When you sign up for an Free Ecards discussion forum, your name or alias is recorded solely for purposes of maintaining your own account within the forums. This information is not used to monitor your activity within a forum, nor is it used to identify you outside the Free Ecards. 

When you register for a contest or other promotion, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. 

When you use co-branded services, or those provided by a third party, within the Free Ecards , your information may be passed to the co-brand or third party provider and their use of your information is subject to their applicable privacy policies. 

##### Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties?

Free Ecards will disclose personal information and/or an IP address, when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: 

  1. Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities and conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Free Ecards, 
  2. Protect and defend the rights or property of the Free Ecards of sites and related properties, or visitors to the Free Ecards of sites and related properties, 
  3. Identify persons who may be violating the law, the Free Ecards legal notice and Web site User Agreement, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing the Free Ecards or its related properties, 
  4. Fulfill a user's order or request. 

Free Ecards uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. Free Ecards reserves the right to transfer all such information in connection with the sale of all or part of Free Ecards's capital stock or assets. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. We are not responsible for such third party privacy policies or how they treat information about their users See below, What else should I know about my privacy when online? See What information do you collect when I register for something. 

#####  Can I send an e-card to my customers? 

In some cases, it may be illegal for an organization or business to use an e-card service to send greetings to its customers. For instance, data privacy laws may forbid a business from disclosing information about customers to a third party – including names and email addresses. So please refer to your agreement with your customers befere using our service 

##### What else should I know about my privacy when online? 

The Free Ecards contains many hyperlinks to third party Web sites. The Free Ecards also contains advertisements of third parties. Free Ecards is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party Web sites or advertisers. Free Ecards does not share any of the individual personal information you provide Free Ecards with the third parties to which Free Ecards links, except as stated elsewhere within this Privacy Policy, although Free Ecards may share general, aggregate data with such third parties (such as how many people use our site). Please check with those Web sites to determine their privacy policy. 

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example through e-mail, discussion lists, or elsewhere - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

##### Your Consent To This Agreement

By using the Free Ecards , you consent to the collection and use of information by Free Ecards as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Please send any questions about Free Ecards Privacy Policy to: admin(at )365greetings.com Please note that your use of the Free Ecards of Web sites is governed by our Legal Notice. Copyright 2003 Free Ecards All Rights Reserved.
